Here we have a function called "invokeTwice".
لدينا هنا دالة تسمى "invokeTwice".
All it does is take in a single callback function over here and calls it two times.
وكل ما تفعله هو أنها تأخذ دالة استدعاء واحدة هنا وتستدعيها مرتين.
Additionally, we also have a dog object. It's pretty simple.
بالإضافة إلى ذلك، لدينا أيضًا كائن dog. إنه أمر بسيط للغاية.
It just has two properties,
لديه خاصيتين فقط،
"age" and "growOneYear", which is
"age" و"growOneYear" وهي فقط
just the method that increments the age property by one.
الطريقة التي تزيد خاصية age بمقدار واحد.
Let's go ahead and try it out. Let's invoke "growOneYear" on dog.
لنتابع ونجرب. دعونا نستدعي "growOneYear" على dog.
Now, let's check the dog's age property,
والآن دعونا نتحقق من خاصية age للكائن dog.
and check out the new ages.
ونتحقق من الأعمار الجديدة.
Great. So it's now six when it used to be five.
رائع. القيمة الآن 6 بينما كانت دائمًا 5.
Now, what if we pass "dog.growOneYear" as a function
الآن، ماذا إذا مرّرنا "dog.growOneYear" كدالة
into "invokeTwice"? Hit enter.
إلى "invokeTwice"؟ وننقر على enter.
Okay. But now let's double check the dog's age property.
حسنًا. لكن الآن دعونا نتحقق مرة أخرى من خاصية age للكائن dog.
As it appears, nothing really changed.
يبدو أنه لم يتغير شيء بالفعل.
The dog's age is still six.
لا يزال عمر الكلب 6.
So why doesn't "invokeTwice" seem to work?
لماذا يبدو أن "invokeTwice" لا تعمل؟
Well, the thing is "invokeTwice" calls a "dog.growOneYear",
حسنًا، السبب أن "invokeTwice" تستدعي "dog.growOneYear"،
but it calls it as a function.
لكنها تستدعيها كدالة.
And as a result, "this",
وكنتيجة لذلك، تُعيّن "this"
it sets the global object rather than the dog object.
الكائن بصفة عامة بدلًا من الكائن dog.
So because using callbacks is such a common pattern,
لذا حيث أن استخدام رد الاستدعاء هو نمط شائِع،
we need a way to save the "this" reference.
نحتاج إلى طريق لحفظ المرجع "this".